<?xml version="1.0"?>
<NPC name= "Roboto">
 <Menu level="1">
  <Line>Ay my g what is up! It's been a while since I saw you, [playerName].</Line>
  <Button text="Talk">
   <Line>
    Hey there! I'm a test NPC. Hopefully, you're reading this right now.
   </Line>
   <Line>
    This is my second line of text!
   </Line>
   <Menu level="2">
    <Line>So this is another menu!</Line>
    <Button text="More Talk">
     <Line>Epic!?</Line>
     <Return back="1"></Return>
    </Button>
    <Button text="Back">
     <Return back="2"></Return>
    </Button>
   </Menu>
  </Button>
  <Button text="What is this?">
   <Line>This is a game called 'arx noctis'. That's latin for fortress of the night. This game is currently EXTREMELY under development.</Line>
   <Line>This means there are probably many bugs, and unimplemented features. This game is a turn-based RPG. To test the battle system, try my test quest!.</Line>
   <Menu level="2">
    <Line>Click any of the following buttons to learn more about this game.</Line>
    <Button text="Weapons?">
     <Line>One of the ways in which you can do more damage in battle, is by using better weapons.</Line>
     <Line>Weapons have a damage range which determines the base damage they do.</Line>
     <Line>They also have an element</Line>
     <Line>The element of the weapon you use does have an effect on damage you do, depending on the resistances of the opponent. Read more about this under 'Battle System?'</Line>
     <Line>Weapons can only be equipped if you meet their level requirement.</Line>
     <Line>That is, once I implement that feature. I'll do it. Eventually.</Line>
     <Line>You can look at a few weapons in your inventory, see information about each one, and equip them.</Line>
     <Return back="1"></Return>
    </Button>
    <Button text="Battle System?">
     <Line>Battles are an integral part of this game. Your damage is affected by your weapon, enemy resistances, and your stats. These stats can be trained (not yet though)</Line>
     <Line>Weapons can also give you stat boosts, and boosts to your resistances. There are 6 stats, which have different effects on your combat ability.</Line>
     <Line>Endurance boosts HP, wisdom boosts MP. Power boosts damage, luck boosts critical/evade chance. Immunity boosts resistances to DoTs, and Recovery boosts healing.</Line>
     <Line>The other important thing in battle is choosing which skills to use. I've not made many, there are like three right now, but oh well.</Line>
     <Return back="1"></Return>
    </Button>
    <Button text="Location??">
     <Line>Right now you're in the town of 'Alteror'. But that's only this location and inside the right building for now. :/</Line>
     <Line>When more is added, hopefully it'll be more obvious that this is a town right on the top of a mountain. Hopefully.</Line>
     <Return back="1"></Return>
    </Button>
    <Button text="Back">
     <Return back="2"></Return>
    </Button>
   </Menu>
  </Button>
  <Button text="Test Quest">
   <Line>This is a test quest. There'll be some enemies n stuff and that's about it.</Line>
   <Menu level="2">
    <Line>Click the quest button to quest!</Line>
    <Quest text="Go!" resource="testQuest"></Quest>
   </Menu>
  </Button>
  <Button text="Heal">
   <Heal></Heal>
  </Button>
  <Button text="Exit">
   <Exit></Exit>
  </Button>
 </Menu>
</NPC>
